http://www.beadofthemonthclub.com/terms.asp

Go!
Minimum Order
There is a $20 minimum order not including shipping.
Ordering from Cocopah
All orders are placed through a secure server to protect your private information. You can place your order online or you can call our office at 928.282.6404 to place your order. If no answer, you may call the store at 928.282.4928. The store is open 7 days a week and very busy. If necessary, we may have to take your number and call back.
Privacy Policy
The personal information you furnish is very important to us. Information provided to Cocopah and the Bead of the Month Club will be kept confidential. We will never sell, rent, or lease your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. To stop receiving our periodic e-mail messages describing updates, new products, or promotional offers, send a reply stating your request.
There are two other services we use, so we want to provide links to their policies.
We send you a monthly email of the Sneak Preview of our Bead and Kit of the Month using MailChimp because it’s trustworthy and efficient. MailChimp's privacy policy is here. Neither we nor MailChimp will ever spam you.
Our online store uses e-commerce software by Volusion. We encourage you to review Volusion's updated privacy policy as well.
Web Site Copyright
All contents, including images, may not be borrowed, copied, reproduced, modified, published or distributed in any form without prior written consent. All rights reserved. Any unauthorized use of the materials on this site may violate copyright and other applicable laws and could result in criminal or civil penalties.
